<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SkinCam</string>

    <string name="description_acne">
    Avoid getting stress or drinking alcohol.\n
    Do not wash your face frequently.\n
    Do not squeeze your acne. Be careful.\n
    please go to hospital as soon as possible.\n
    </string>

    <string name="description_Actinic_Keratosis">
    #########Strongly Recommand!! ##############\n
    Since the symptoms need to be confirmed based on a biopsy, it is recommended that you go to the hospital quickly and do a detailed examination.\n

    ① Cryotherapy\n
    A method of freezing the surface of the skin with liquid nitrogen to allow the skin to peel off and be replaced by new skin. The main side effect is redness of the skin, but it is the most widely used treatment.\n



    ② local chemotherapy\n
    It is treated by applying a topical anti-cancer cream or lotion (such as 5-fluorouracil) to the affected area of   the skin. Red spots may remain on the treated area for a period of time.\n



    ③ Phototherapy\n
    First, a chemical is applied to the skin, and after 2-3 hours, a blue light is lit on the actinic keratosis area to allow the chemical to destroy the lesion. Localized erythema may appear and disappear for several days after treatment.\n

    ④ Chemical peeling\n
    When a chemical solution is applied to the skin lesion, the skin peels off over several days before new skin regenerates. The doctor selects the necessary chemical solution for the depth of peeling in mild, moderate, or moderate peeling according to the lesion and performs peeling. As an important side effect, redness and swelling of the skin may persist for a period of time after treatment.\n



    ⑤ laser treatment\n
    It is a treatment that removes the skin surface to the desired depth with a carbon dioxide laser. As a side effect, your skin may become red. A recovery period of 1 to 2 weeks is required.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Atopic_Dermatitis">
    Even if it causes a lot of itching, it is recommended to cool off with a cold compress\n
    and avoid scratching as much as possible.\n

    Treatment for atopic dermatitis requires treatment with immunosuppressants and steroids.\n
    As these drugs are strictly limited to individuals,\n
    it is recommended to consult with a specialist and take appropriate measures.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Bullous_Disease">
    Apply the ointment well at the beginning and watch the progress to see the improvement.\n

    If there is no improvement after 3 days,\n
    please go to a nearby large hospital and have a biopsy done as soon as possible\n
    </string>

    <string name="description_Cellulitis_Impetigo">
    It is a disease caused by infection by bacteria.\n
    After applying the ointment, please keep it clean and do not go out because it is an infectious disease.\n

    If it does not get better after 7 days,\n
    go to the nearest hospital and get a prescription for antibiotics.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Eczema">
    There is no radical cure. To relieve symptoms, you need to get rid of the cause of the disease.\n

    We recommend that you apply a moisturizing cream or ointment and wear gloves when working.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Exanthem">
    There is no specific treatment for sudden rashes other than symptomatic treatment.\n
    It usually heals naturally in 6-7 days.\n
    If the child has a high fever and is nauseous, antipyretics are administered and sufficient fluids are supplied.\n
    Acetaminophen and ibuprofen can be used as antipyretics, but aspirin should be avoided.\n

    Sudden rashes heal spontaneously without any special treatment.\n
    The rash formed at this time does not peel off, leaving no scars.\n
    In rare cases, febrile convulsions may occur due to severe high fever,\n
    so it is important to administer antipyretics when high fever is present.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Hair_Loss">
    The cause of alopecia areata remains unclear.\n
    However, mental stress, autoimmunity, and endocrine disorders are presumed to be the cause or trigger.\n

    The prognosis of alopecia areata is worse when hair loss occurs at a young age or\n
    when the area of hair loss increases.\n
    Alopecia areata often gets better on its own when the size of the lesion is small.\n
    If the area of the lesion is large or the hair falls out a lot, treatment is recommended.\n

    Treatment includes topical application of steroids and intralesional injections.\n
    Applying a solution of minoxidil may also help with treatment.\n
    If hair loss is rapid and widespread, steroids are given by mouth.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Herpes_HPV">
    Pills, intravenous injections, ointments, etc.\n
    are selected and used according to the symptoms of the disease.\n
    However, these antiviral drugs do not completely eliminate the herpes simplex virus,\n
    and are used to relieve symptoms caused by the virus or prevent recurrence of symptoms.\n

    Avoid contact with other people\'s bodily fluids, and be careful as\n
    it can also be transmitted through sexual contact.\n
    In order to prevent recurrence of herpes simplex type 1, stress management is required on a daily basis.\n
    In particular, for herpes simplex type 2, which recurs well,\n
    antiviral drugs should be administered for a long time to continuously suppress the proliferation of the virus.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Light_Disease">
    There is no definitive treatment for hereditary metabolic disorders.\n
    It is important to avoid the sun\'s rays to protect your skin. Sunglasses, long sleeves and pants,\n
     and sunscreen lotion (SPF20 or higher) are helpful,\n
    especially in tropical areas where the sun\'s rays are strong.\n
    Glasses, etc., can help correct your vision. Surgery is performed to correct the strabismus.\n
    This is only a cosmetic correction and has no effect on vision correction.\n

    Genetic counseling is helpful for patients and their families.\n
    Additional treatments include symptomatic therapy,\n
    which aims to relieve symptoms,\n
    and supportive therapy to control and alleviate various side effects or complications.\n

    </string>


    <string name="description_Lupus">
    There is no way to prevent the development of lupus.\n
    However, since lupus has a genetic tendency, if there is a patient with lupus in the family,\n
    it can be diagnosed early through appropriate examination and antibody test.\n
    Complications of lupus can be prevented by vaccination against influenza and pneumococcus,\n
    and by controlling factors related to arteriosclerosis,\n
    such as hypertension, blood sugar, and lipid metabolism disorders.\n
    It is also important to prevent osteoporosis\n
    if steroids are used for a long period of time during treatment.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Melanoma_Skin_Cancer">
    ##################Caution############################\n
    There is no way to self-medicate. Run to the big university hospital right now!\n
    ################## Caution########################\n
    For an accurate diagnosis of skin cancer,\n
    a skin biopsy in which a portion of the skin lesion is removed and examined under local anesthesia is required.\n
    In addition to chest X-ray and abdominal ultrasonography, detailed examinations\n
    such as radioisotope tests, CT scans, and\n
    MRIs can determine the depth of tumor infiltration (spreading around) and the extent of disease spread such as metastases .\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Nail_Fungus">
    Wash your hands and feet thoroughly to avoid spreading the infection to other areas.\n

    Athlete\'s foot is contagious, so do not share socks, etc. with other people, and avoid shoes that are too tight.\n

    Rinse well with warm water and then dry it not to get wet.\n

    If you cut your nails too short, you risk infection, so be careful.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Contact_Dermatitis">
    In most cases, the prognosis is very good as long as the substances that promote contact dermatitis are identified and avoided.\n
    With proper treatment and avoidance of exposure, symptoms will improve within 2-3 weeks.\n
    However, prolonged exposure to harmful chemicals and allergens can lead to chronic contact dermatitis lasting for years.\n
    Therefore, if symptoms appear, you should seek treatment as soon as possible.\n

    Please go to the nearest hospital as soon as possible.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Psoriasis">
    Avoid skin irritation or damage\n
    Skin irritation or damage that occurs in daily life can cause or worsen psoriasis.\n
    Therefore, it is important for psoriasis patients to be careful to avoid such skin damage in their daily life.\n
    Prevents skin from drying out\n
    The skin of psoriasis dries easily because the moisture and fat of the normal skin are not supplied well,\n
     and the moisture is lost faster than normal people.\n
    The result is dry skin, which can make psoriasis worse.\n
    One of the reasons that seasonal psoriasis gets worse in winter is that everyone tends to have dry skin in winter.\n
    So, it\'s important to remember that preventing dry skin can be both preventative and treat psoriasis.\n
    Avoid emotional stress and overwork\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Scabies_Lyme_Disease">
    Lyme disease is usually curable if treated early.\n
    However, complications may occur if the diagnosis of Lyme disease is delayed\n
     or if antibiotic treatment is not performed properly,\n
    if Lyme disease develops along with other diseases, or\n
    if the Lyme disease patient has weakened immunity.\n
    In these cases, even with antibiotic treatment, fatigue, musculoskeletal pain,\n
    and neurological symptoms may persist for years. It rarely leads to death.\n

    If the symptoms persist for several weeks,\n
    we hope that you will be aware of the situation through a thorough examination at the hospital\n
    before it is too late.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Seborrheic_Keratoses">
    It can be treated by cryotherapy using liquid nitrogen\n
    or chemical peeling using trichloroacetic acid (TCA). In addition,\n
    laser therapy and electrodrying are also effective. Surgical excision is not often used,\n
    but if it is not typical and certain seborrheic keratosis,\n
    a histological examination should be performed to differentiate malignant tumors such as melanoma.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Systemic_Disease">
    If lupus causes mild long-term involvement such as hair loss, skin rash, joint pain, arthritis, pleurisy,\n
    and pericarditis, it can be controlled with nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs,\n
    antimalarial drugs, and small amounts of steroids.\n
    In the case of serious organ involvement such as nephritis, myocarditis, lupus pneumonia, and cerebrovasculitis, active treatment\n
    with high-dose steroids and strong immunosuppressants is required in addition to the above drugs.\n

    If the symptoms persist, tests to diagnose lupus include autoantibody tests with special blood tests,\n
    general blood tests, liver function tests, and kidney function tests.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Fungal_Infection">
    Vaginal yeast infections are caused by overgrowth of Candida.\n
    These yeasts are usually present in the vagina in small numbers.\n
    It is not classified as a sexually transmitted disease,\n
    but it may appear more frequently in people who are sexually active.\n
     Risk factors include antibiotic intake, pregnancy, diabetes, and AIDS.\n
    A high intake of monosaccharides can also be a contributing factor.\n
    Personal hygiene, such as tight clothing, clothing type, or the like, is not considered a factor.\n
    Diagnosis is made by testing a sample of vaginal discharge.\n
    Symptoms are similar to those of STDs, chlamydia, and gonorrhea, so testing may be recommended.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Urticaria_Hives">
    Urticaria is a disease characterized by sudden onset wheal and angioedema,\n
    and it is known that about 20% of the population experience it at least once in their lifetime.\n
    Urticaria is classified into acute and chronic according to the duration of characteristic symptoms\n
    such as wheal, angioedema, and skin itching.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Vascular_Tumor">
    Most infant hemangiomas will degenerate over a period of growth.\n
    Therefore, unless there is a special area that causes functional impairment,\n
    natural degeneration can be waited. However, as it swells and improves, traces of hemangioma are left.\n
    In addition, when complications such as severe bleeding, thrombocytopenia, food intake, breathing\n
    and urine excretion, limb function, and visual field impairment due to the location of the lesion occur,\n
    treatment is required. There are laser treatment, steroid injection or oral administration, propranolol application\n
    and oral administration, interferon alpha treatment, etc.,\n
    and surgical treatment can be considered for scars remaining after degeneration of hemangiomas.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Vasculitis">
    Vasculitis usually has a good general clinical course, but recurrent purpura is more likely to develop kidney complications.\n
    In particular, in the case of adults 16 years of age or older, the prognosis for irritable purpura is poor,\n
    so it is recommended to check for proteinuria or\n
    hematuria through a urine test every 3 months to detect chronic renal failure early.\n

    In many studies worldwide, it has been confirmed that the outcome of renal involvement is the same in the group taking and not taking steroids.\n
    You\'ll never know that steroids are not the best treatment drug.\n
    On the other hand, complications from long-term use must also be considered.\n

    </string>

    <string name="description_Viral_Infection">
    In the treatment of RS virus infection, there is no preventive vaccine or antiviral agent for RS virus,\n
    so conservative treatment according to the symptoms takes priority.\n
    Ribavirin aspiration therapy may be helpful for hospitalized infants. In addition,\n
    RS virus immunoglobulin is injected during winter to prevent infection for high-risk groups\n
    such as children with bronchopulmonary dysplasia or congenital heart disease, or\n
    monoclonal anti-RSV antibody is administered monthly from September to March when RS virus is prevalent.\n
    It is also administered intramuscularly.
    </string>
</resources>